Guide to the Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York Records WAG.009
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Addendum, 1957-2004; 107103
  - Subseries F: General Files, 1957-2004; 107104
    - Bronx Community College Chapter: Publicity, 1984-1997; 107859 (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter, 1979-1981; 107858 (Box 155, Folder 13)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter, 1982-1984; 107857 (Box 155, Folder 14)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter, 1985-1987; 107856 (Box 155, Folder 15)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter, 1988-1992; 107855 (Box 155, Folder 16)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter, 1993-1997; 107854 (Box 155, Folder 17)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter: Boris, Richard, 1995-1999; 107853 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter: Clippings, 1979-1988; 107852 (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter: Grievances, 1978-1982; 107851 (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter: Grievances, 1983-1986; 107850 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter: Newsletter, 1973-1980; 107849 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter: Publicity, 1987-1998; 107848 (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Brooklyn Educational Opportunity Center, 1997-1998; 107847 (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Brooklyn Equal Opportunity Center, 1972-1986; 107846 (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Brooklyn Equal Opportunity Center, 1987-1996; 107845 (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Brooklyn Urban Center, 1989-1999; 107844 (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Budget: City University of New York (CUNY), 1979-1980; 107843 (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - Budget: CUNY (I), 1981-1982; 107842 (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Budget: CUNY (II), 1981-1982; 107841 (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - Budget: CUNY, 1982-1983; 107840 (Box 156, Folder 14)
    - Budget: CUNY, 1985-1986; 107839 (Box 156, Folder 15)
    - Budget: CUNY, 1991-1992; 107838 (Box 156, Folder 16)
    - Budget: CUNY-Clippings, 1990-1999; 107837 (Box 156, Folder 17)
    - Budget: CUNY-Executive Budget, 1991-1992; 107836 (Box 156, Folder 18)
    - Budget: CUNY-Lobbying, 1991-1992; 107835 (Box 156, Folder 19)
    - Budget: CUNY-Midyear Cuts, 1991-1992; 107834 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Budget: CUNY-New York City, 1991-1992; 107833 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Budget: CUNY-Protests, 1991-1992; 107832 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Budget: CUNY-Published Plans, 1983-1986; 107831 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Budget: CUNY-State, 1991-1992; 107830 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Budget Crisis, 1973-1976; 107829 (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Budget: Federal, 1982; 107828 (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - Budget: Federal-Clippings (I), 1981-1982; 107827 (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Budget: Federal-Clippings (II), 1981-1982; 107826 (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - Budget: Federal-Clippings (I), 1983-1999; 107825 (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Budget: Federal-Clippings (II), 1983-1999; 107824 (Box 157, Folder 11)
    - Budget: New York City, 1981; 107823 (Box 157, Folder 12)
    - Budget: New York City-Clippings, 1986-1999; 107822 (Box 157, Folder 13)
    - Budget: Professional Staff Congress (PSC), 1982; 107821 (Box 157, Folder 14)
    - Budget: State, 1982; 107820 (Box 157, Folder 15)
    - Budget: State-Clippings (I), 1983-1999; 107819 (Box 157, Folder 16)
    - Budget: State-Clippings (II), 1983-1999; 107818 (Box 157, Folder 17)
    - Burnout, 1982; 107817 (Box 157, Folder 18)
    - Business Managers, 1974-1992; 107816 (Box 157, Folder 19)
    - Bylaws: City University of New York Board of Trustees, 1993; 107815 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Bylaws Committee, 1970-1972; 107814 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Calandera Institute (I), 1980-1996; 107813 (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Calandera Institute (II), 1980-1996; 107812 (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Caldwell Building, 1981; 107811 (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Campbell, Claude, 1979; 107810 (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - Campbell, Claude, 1980-1981; 107809 (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - Campbell, Claude, 1982; 107808 (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - Campbell, Claude, 1983-1984; 107807 (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - Candidates, 1982; 107806 (Box 158, Folder 10)
    - Cantor, Arnold, 1980; 107805 (Box 158, Folder 11)
    - Cantor, Arnold, 1981; 107804 (Box 158, Folder 12)
    - Cantor, Arnold, 1982; 107803 (Box 158, Folder 13)
    - Cantor, Arnold, 1983; 107802 (Box 158, Folder 14)
    - Cantor, Arnold, 1984; 107801 (Box 158, Folder 15)
    - Cantor, Arnold (I), 1987; 107800 (Box 158, Folder 16)
    - Cantor, Arnold (II), 1987; 107799 (Box 158, Folder 17)
    - Cantor, Arnold (I), 1988; 107798 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Cantor, Arnold (II), 1988; 107797 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Cantor, Arnold, 1989; 107796 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Cantor, Arnold, 1990; 107795 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Censorship, 1975-1982; 107794 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Censorship, 1983-1985; 107793 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Censorship, 1986-1987; 107792 (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - Censorship, 1989-1992; 107791 (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Censorship, 1993-1997; 107790 (Box 159, Folder 9)
    - Census Data, 1991-1994; 107789 (Box 159, Folder 10)
    - Center for Worker Education, 1977-1996; 107788 (Box 159, Folder 11)
    - Central Labor Council (CLC): Correspondence, 1996-2000; 107787 (Box 159, Folder 12)
    - Central Office Chapter, 1980-1987; 107786 (Box 159, Folder 13)
    - Central Office Chapter, 1988; 107785 (Box 159, Folder 14)
    - Central Office Chapter, 1989-1998; 107784 (Box 159, Folder 15)
    - Chapey, Geraldine, 1984-1990; 107783 (Box 159, Folder 16)
    - Chapter Chairperson Meetings, 1980-1982; 107782 (Box 159, Folder 17)
    - Chapter Chairperson Meetings, 1983; 107781 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Chapter Chairperson Meetings, 1984; 107780 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Chapter Chairperson Meetings, 1985-1986; 107779 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Chapter Chairperson Meetings, 1987-1989; 107778 (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - City College Chapter, 1973-1976; 107777 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - City College Chapter, 1977-1983; 107776 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - City College Chapter, 1984-1991; 107775 (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - City College Chapter, 1992-1993; 107774 (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - City College Chapter, 1994-1999; 107773 (Box 160, Folder 9)
    - City College Chapter: Boris, Richard, 1995-1999; 107772 (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - City College Chapter: Chinese Exchange Program, 1983; 107771 (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - City College Chapter: Counselors, 1985-1988; 107770 (Box 160, Folder 12)
    - City College Chapter: Grievances, 1976-1983; 107769 (Box 160, Folder 13)
    - City College Chapter: Grievances, 1984-1992; 107768 (Box 160, Folder 14)
    - City College Chapter: Newsletter, 1974-1980; 107767 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - City College Chapter: Publicity, 1981-1992; 107766 (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - City College Chapter: Publicity, 1993-1999; 107765 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - City Health Plans, 1994; 107764 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - City University of New York (CUNY), 1970-1978; 107763 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - CUNY: Alumni, 1992-1995; 107762 (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - CUNY: Bilingualism, 1997-1999; 107761 (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - CUNY: Board of Trustees, 1994-2000; 107760 (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - CUNY: Boris, Richard, 1995-1998; 107759 (Box 161, Folder 9)
    - CUNY: Budget, 1973-1988; 107758 (Box 161, Folder 10)
    - CUNY: Community Colleges, 1995-1999; 107757 (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - CUNY: CUNY Talk, 1997; 107756 (Box 161, Folder 12)
    - CUNY: Department Chairmen, 1973-1977; 107755 (Box 161, Folder 13)
    - CUNY: Governance, 1970-1979; 107754 (Box 161, Folder 14)
    - CUNY: Grievances, 1976-1988; 107753 (Box 161, Folder 15)
    - CUNY: Grievances-Circumventing Agreements (I), 1976-1982; 107752 (Box 161, Folder 16)
    - CUNY: Grievances-Circumventing Agreements (II), 1976-1982; 107751 (Box 161, Folder 17)
    - CUNY: Language Immersion Program, 1996; 107750 (Box 161, Folder 18)
    - CUNY: Library Association, 1979-1989; 107749 (Box 161, Folder 19)
    - CUNY: New Visions Committee, 1996-1998; 107748 (Box 161, Folder 20)
    - CUNY: Office of Budget and Finance, 1979-1995; 107747 (Box 161, Folder 21)
    - CUNY: Presidents, 1976-1978; 107746 (Box 161, Folder 22)
    - CUNY: Rank and File, Undated; 107745 (Box 161, Folder 23)
    - CUNY: Students, 1969-1988; 107744 (Box 161, Folder 24)
    - City University Union Caucus (CUUC), 1970-1979; 107743 (Box 161, Folder 25)
    - CUUC, 1982-1987; 107742 (Box 161, Folder 26)
    - CUUC: Election Materials, 1986; 107741 (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - Clarion, 1997-1999; 107740 (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Clarion: Meetings, 1990-1997; 107739 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Clarion: Policy, 1974-1987; 107738 (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Clarion: Reports, 1985-1991; 107737 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Clarion: Special Election Issue, 1982; 107736 (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - Clippings (I), 1994-1999; 107735 (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - Clippings (II), 1994-1999; 107734 (Box 162, Folder 8)
    - Co-Affiliates, 1982-1987; 107733 (Box 162, Folder 9)
    - Co-Affiliates, 1988-1990; 107732 (Box 162, Folder 10)
    - Co-Affiliates, 1991-1997; 107731 (Box 162, Folder 11)
    - Coalition of Municipal Unions (I), 1978-1984; 107730 (Box 162, Folder 12)
    - Coalition of Municipal Unions (II), 1978-1984; 107729 (Box 162, Folder 13)
    - Collective Bargaining, 1972-1974; 107728 (Box 162, Folder 14)
    - Collective Bargaining (I), 1975; 107727 (Box 162, Folder 15)
    - Collective Bargaining (II), 1975; 107726 (Box 162, Folder 16)
    - Collective Bargaining, 1976; 107725 (Box 162, Folder 17)
    - Collective Bargaining: Clippings, 1978-1995; 107724 (Box 162, Folder 18)
    - College Lab Technicians Chapter, 1976-1978; 107723 (Box 162, Folder 19)
    - College Lab Technicians Chapter, 1979-1982; 107722 (Box 162, Folder 20)
    - College Lab Technicians Chapter, 1983-1985; 107721 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - College Lab Technicians Chapter, 1986-1998; 107720 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - College Now Program, 1999-2000; 107719 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - College of Staten Island (CSI) Chapter, 1980-1983; 107718 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - CSI Chapter, 1984-1990; 107717 (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - CSI Chapter, 1991-1999; 107716 (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - CSI Chapter: Clippings, 1982-1998; 107715 (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - CSI Chapter: Grievances, 1981-1989; 107714 (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - CSI Chapter: Newsletter, 1976-1980; 107713 (Box 163, Folder 9)
    - College Physicians, 1958-1974; 107712 (Box 163, Folder 10)
    - College Preparatory Initiative, 1991-1995; 107711 (Box 163, Folder 11)
    - Colleges and Universities, 1987-1998; 107710 (Box 163, Folder 12)
    - College Teaching, 1988-1990; 107709 (Box 163, Folder 13)
    - Commencements, 1982; 107708 (Box 163, Folder 14)
    - Committee for Chapter Conformity, 1977-1978; 107707 (Box 163, Folder 15)
    - Committee for Public Higher Education (CPHE), 1973-1978; 107706 (Box 163, Folder 16)
    - CPHE, 1983; 107705 (Box 163, Folder 17)
    - CPHE, 1991-1992; 107704 (Box 163, Folder 18)
    - CPHE, 1995-1998; 107703 (Box 163, Folder 19)
    - CPHE: Tuition Study, 1982; 107702 (Box 163, Folder 20)
    - Committee for SUNY-CUNY Unity, 1978; 107701 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Contract Negotiations, 1972-1974; 107700 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Committee on Part-Time Personnel, 1983-1988; 107699 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1972-1996; 107698 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Community Colleges, 1958-1999; 107697 (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - Computers, 1983-1990; 107696 (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - Conference of Academic Unionists, 1981; 107695 (Box 164, Folder 7)
    - Conference: Professors and Unions, 1981; 107694 (Box 164, Folder 8)
    - Conferences, 1982-1983; 107693 (Box 164, Folder 9)
    - Contract Administration Guidelines and Procedures, 1972-1995; 107692 (Box 164, Folder 10)
    - Contract Demands Committee, 1986-1989; 107691 (Box 164, Folder 11)
    - Contract Negotiations, 1986-1999; 107690 (Box 164, Folder 12)
    - Contracts, 1982-1983; 107689 (Box 164, Folder 13)
    - Contracts (I), 1984-1985; 107688 (Box 164, Folder 14)
    - Contracts (II), 1984-1985; 107687 (Box 164, Folder 15)
    - Contracts: Bargaining Research, 1977-1981; 107686 (Box 164, Folder 16)
    - Contracts: Finalized, 1980-1990; 107685 (Box 164, Folder 17)
    - Contract Vote, 1973; 107684 (Box 164, Folder 18)
    - Contributions, 1987-1994; 107683 (Box 164, Folder 19)
    - Conventions, Sep 1982; 107682 (Box 164, Folder 20)
    - Copyright Law, 1983-1988; 107681 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Copyright: PSC Publications, Jun 1905-1990; 107680 (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Cornell University, 1972-1984; 107679 (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1997; 107678 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Congratulations and Complaints, 1974-1984; 107677 (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Executive Council, 1973-1978; 107676 (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Faxes, 1995-1997; 107675 (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Inter-Office, 1972-1980; 107674 (Box 165, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Membership Mailings, 1972-1975; 107673 (Box 165, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Membership Mailings, 1976-1978; 107672 (Box 165, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Membership Mailings, 1979-1982; 107671 (Box 165, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Membership Mailings, 1990-1997; 107670 (Box 165, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Stein, Andrew, 1978; 107669 (Box 165, Folder 13)
    - Corsi Labor-Management Relations Institute, 1975; 107668 (Box 165, Folder 14)
    - Council of Presidents, 1973-1985; 107667 (Box 165, Folder 15)
    - Council of Supervisor and Administrators of the City of New York, 1975; 107666 (Box 165, Folder 16)
    - Counselors, 1993; 107665 (Box 165, Folder 17)
    - Credit Union, 1981-1986; 107664 (Box 165, Folder 18)
    - Crisis Bulletin, 1976; 107663 (Box 165, Folder 19)
    - CUNY Association of Reading Educators (CARE), 1982; 107662 (Box 165, Folder 20)
    - CUNY Courier, 1973-1976; 107661 (Box 165, Folder 21)
    - CUNY Legislative Action Council (CLAC), 1982-1983; 107660 (Box 165, Folder 22)
    - Curriculum, 1985-1999; 107659 (Box 165, Folder 23)
    - Defense Fund, 1976-1978; 107658 (Box 165, Folder 24)
    - Deferred Wages, 1987-1991; 107657 (Box 165, Folder 25)
    - Delegate Assembly Minutes, 1990-1999; 107656 (Box 165, Folder 26)
    - Democratic Party, 1974; 107655 (Box 165, Folder 27)
    - Disclosure Bill, 1973-1975; 107654 (Box 165, Folder 28)
    - Distance Learning, 1996-1998; 107653 (Box 165, Folder 29)
    - District Council (DC) 37, 1971-1999; 107652 (Box 165, Folder 30)
    - Document Retrieval, 1987-1991; 107651 (Box 165, Folder 31)
    - Dues, 1973-1993; 107650 (Box 165, Folder 32)
    - Dues Increase, 1982; 107649 (Box 165, Folder 33)
    - Dues-Rebate Notice, 1983; 107648 (Box 165, Folder 34)
    - Dues Revision, 1978-1983; 107647 (Box 165, Folder 35)
    - Dullea, Henrik: Special Assistant to Governor, 1977-1979; 107646 (Box 165, Folder 36)
    - Dushane Fund Report, 1974-1975; 107645 (Box 165, Folder 37)
    - Early Childhood Education, 1975; 107644 (Box 165, Folder 38)
    - Early Retirement, 1984-1998; 107643 (Box 165, Folder 39)
    - Early Retirement Incentives (I), 1990-1997; 107642 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Early Retirement Incentives (II), 1990-1997; 107641 (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Educational Resources Information Center (ERIC), 1999; 107640 (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Educational Consolidation and Improvement Act Advisory Council, 1982; 107639 (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Education Funding, 1992-1993; 107638 (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - Education Reform, 1988-1989; 107637 (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - Education Statistics, 1991-1998; 107636 (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - Election, 1982; 107635 (Box 166, Folder 8)
    - Election, 1991; 107634 (Box 166, Folder 9)
    - Election (I), 1997; 107633 (Box 166, Folder 10)
    - Election (II), 1997; 107632 (Box 166, Folder 11)
    - Election: American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1982; 107631 (Box 166, Folder 12)
    - Election and Credentials Committee, 1980-1987; 107630 (Box 166, Folder 13)
    - Election: California, 1982; 107629 (Box 166, Folder 14)
    - Election: National, 1982; 107628 (Box 166, Folder 15)
    - Election: Professional Staff Congress (PSC), 1983; 107627 (Box 166, Folder 16)
    - Election Results, 1982; 107626 (Box 166, Folder 17)
    - Enrollment, 1982-1994; 107625 (Box 166, Folder 18)
    - Equality for CUNY, 1975; 107624 (Box 166, Folder 19)
    - Equal Rights Amendment, Undated; 107623 (Box 166, Folder 20)
    - Executive Council Agendas, 1992-1999; 107622 (Box 166, Folder 21)
    - Executive Council Minutes, 1982-1986; 107621 (Box 166, Folder 22)
    - Executive Council Minutes, 1990-1999; 107620 (Box 166, Folder 23)
    - Faculty and Staff Relations (I), 1974-1989; 107619 (Box 166, Folder 24)
    - Faculty and Staff Relations (II), 1974-1989; 107618 (Box 166, Folder 25)
    - Faculty and Staff Relations (I), 1990-1999; 107617 (Box 166, Folder 26)
    - Faculty and Staff Relations (II), 1990-1999; 107616 (Box 166, Folder 27)
    - Faculty and Staff Relations (III), 1990-1999; 107615 (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Development Program, 1983-1987; 107614 (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Research Award Program, 1972-1989; 107613 (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Research Award Program (I), 1990; 107612 (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Research Award Program (II), 1990; 107611 (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Research Award Program, 1991-2000; 107610 (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - Feminist Conference, 1983; 107609 (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - Finance Committee, 1990-1994; 107608 (Box 167, Folder 8)
    - Finance Committee: Minutes and Agendas, 1973-1982; 107607 (Box 167, Folder 9)
    - Financial: Certificates of Deposit, 1990-1998; 107606 (Box 167, Folder 10)
    - Financial Statements, 1980-2000; 107605 (Box 167, Folder 11)
    - Five Borough Institute, 1999; 107604 (Box 167, Folder 12)
    - Ford, Gerald R., 1975; 107603 (Box 167, Folder 13)
    - Fratti, Mario, 1982; 107602 (Box 167, Folder 14)
    - Free Tuition, 1973; 107601 (Box 167, Folder 15)
    - Friends of CUNY, 1999; 107600 (Box 167, Folder 16)
    - Gay Academic Union, 1973; 107599 (Box 167, Folder 17)
    - Graduate School Chapter, 1972-1973; 107598 (Box 167, Folder 18)
    - Graduate School Chapter, 1994-1999; 107597 (Box 167, Folder 19)
    - Graduate School Chapter: Center for Advanced Study in Education, 1978-1986; 107596 (Box 167, Folder 20)
    - Graduate School Chapter: Boris, Richard, 1997-1999; 107595 (Box 167, Folder 21)
    - Grayson, Gerald (I), 1976-2000; 107594 (Box 167, Folder 22)
    - Grayson, Gerald (II), 1976-2000; 107593 (Box 167, Folder 23)
    - Grievance Committee: Four-Day Week Plan, 1978-1983; 107592 (Box 167, Folder 24)
    - Grievance Counselors, 1972-1986; 107591 (Box 167, Folder 25)
    - Grievance Policy Committee, 1973-1977; 107590 (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Grievance Policy Committee: Correspondence-Cantor, Arnold, 1985-1986; 107589 (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Grievances, 1995-2000; 107588 (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Grievances: Gellnof Decision, 1975; 107587 (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - Grievance Summaries, 1984-1989; 107586 (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Grievance Workshop, 1974-1979; 107585 (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Helmsley-Spear Incorporated, 1970-1977; 107584 (Box 168, Folder 7)
    - Higher Education: Collective Bargaining, 1974-1984; 107583 (Box 168, Folder 8)
    - Higher Education: Curriculum, 1968-1992; 107582 (Box 168, Folder 9)
    - Higher Education Excellence (I), 1982-1997; 107581 (Box 168, Folder 10)
    - Higher Education Excellence (II), 1982-1997; 107580 (Box 168, Folder 11)
    - Higher Education Funding (I), 1974-1996; 107579 (Box 168, Folder 12)
    - Higher Education Funding (II), 1974-1996; 107578 (Box 168, Folder 13)
    - Higher Education International, 1984-1993; 107577 (Box 168, Folder 14)
    - Higher Education Officers (HEOs), 1980-1983; 107576 (Box 168, Folder 15)
    - HEOs, 1984-1988; 107575 (Box 168, Folder 16)
    - HEOs, 1989-1998; 107574 (Box 168, Folder 17)
    - HEOs: Correspondence, 1974-1997; 107573 (Box 168, Folder 18)
    - High School Principals, 1978; 107572 (Box 168, Folder 19)
    - Histadrut, 1974-1995; 107571 (Box 168, Folder 20)
    - Historical Records, 1937-1991; 107570 (Box 168, Folder 21)
    - Hostos Community College Chapter, 1976-1979; 107569 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - Hostos Community College Chapter, 1980-1982; 107568 (Box 169, Folder 2)
    - Hostos Community College Chapter, 1983-1984; 107567 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Hostos Community College Chapter, 1985-1989; 107566 (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - Hostos Community College Chapter, 1990-1993; 107565 (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - Hostos Community College Chapter, 1994-1995; 107564 (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - Hostos Community College Chapter, 1996; 107563 (Box 169, Folder 7)
    - Hostos Community College Chapter (I), 1997; 107562 (Box 169, Folder 8)
    - Hostos Community College Chapter (II), 1997; 107561 (Box 169, Folder 9)
    - Hostos Community College Chapter, 1998; 107560 (Box 169, Folder 10)
    - Hostos Community College Chapter, 1999; 107559 (Box 169, Folder 11)
    - Hostos Community College Chapter: Boris, Richard, 1996-2000; 107558 (Box 169, Folder 12)
    - Hostos Community College Chapter: Clippings, 1977-1997; 107557 (Box 169, Folder 13)
    - Hostos Community College Chapter: Grievances, 1979-1981; 107556 (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Hostos Community College Chapter: Newsletter, 1973-1980; 107555 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Howe Report on City University of New York (CUNY), 1978; 107554 (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Hunter Campus Schools, 1971-1994; 107553 (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - Hunter College Chapter, 1973-1978; 107552 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Hunter College Chapter (I), 1981; 107551 (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Hunter College Chapter (II), 1981; 107550 (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - Hunter College Chapter (I), 1982; 107549 (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Hunter College Chapter (II), 1982; 107548 (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Hunter College Chapter (I), 1983; 107547 (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - Hunter College Chapter (II), 1983; 107546 (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Hunter College Chapter, 1984-1985; 107545 (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - Hunter College Chapter, 1986-1987; 107544 (Box 170, Folder 13)
    - Hunter College Chapter, 1988-1989; 107543 (Box 170, Folder 14)
    - Hunter College Chapter, 1990; 107542 (Box 170, Folder 15)
    - Hunter College Chapter, 1991; 107541 (Box 170, Folder 16)
    - Hunter College Chapter, 1992-1993; 107540 (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Hunter College Chapter, 1994; 107539 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Hunter College Chapter, 1995-1998; 107538 (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Hunter College Chapter: Boris, Richard, 1983-2000; 107537 (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Hunter College Chapter: Clippings, 1990-1997; 107536 (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - Hunter College Chapter: English Language Institute, 1982-1987; 107535 (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Hunter College Chapter: Grievances, 1977-1984; 107534 (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - Hunter College Chapter: Grievances, 1985; 107533 (Box 171, Folder 8)
    - Hunter College Chapter: Grievances, 1988-1990; 107532 (Box 171, Folder 9)
    - Hunter College Chapter: Newsletter, 1973-1980; 107531 (Box 171, Folder 10)
    - Improper Practices, 1969-1972; 107530 (Box 171, Folder 11)
    - Improper Practices (I), 1973-1975; 107529 (Box 171, Folder 12)
    - Improper Practices (II), 1973-1975; 107528 (Box 171, Folder 13)
    - Improper Practices, 1976; 107527 (Box 171, Folder 14)
    - Improper Practices, 1994-1997; 107526 (Box 171, Folder 15)
    - Individual Retirement Account (IRA), 1983; 107525 (Box 171, Folder 16)
    - Internal Relations Research Association, 1974-1981; 107524 (Box 171, Folder 17)
    - International Education, 1996; 107523 (Box 171, Folder 18)
    - International Foundation Employee Benefits, 1999; 107522 (Box 171, Folder 19)
    - International Longshoremen's Association, 1980; 107521 (Box 171, Folder 20)
    - International Unions, 1987-1989; 107520 (Box 171, Folder 21)